（忆往昔）
萨姆 扮演路西法
Sam starring as lucifer.
迪恩 扮演米迦勒
Dean starring as michael.
你们要适应 承担你们的责任
You're gonna suck it up, accept your responsibilities,
扮演好命运所选的角色
And play the roles that destiny has chosen for you.
为什么木桩没杀死你
Why didn't the stake kill you?
我是恶作剧精灵啊 或许你根本不是
I am the trickster. But maybe you're not.
- 你好啊 加百列 - 大天使吗
- Hello, gabriel. - The archangel?
这绝不是你们弟兄间的拳击赛
This isn't about some prizefight between your brothers.
这就是你
This is about you.
不敢抵抗你的家族而已
Being too afraid to stand up to your family!
你是不是要去做一些蠢事
Are you gonna do something stupid?
- 比方说 - 去找米迦勒
- Like what? - Michael stupid.
走吧 萨姆
Come on, Sam.
事情会变得非常糟
Things are about to get really bad.
我接下来要见的人
The people that I'm gonna see next,
他们要是想从我身上拿走一些东西
They're not gonna get anything from me.
就必须先答应我的条件
Without agreeing to a few conditions.
不管你打算干什么 别去
Whatever you're thinking of doing, don't do it.
我必须去
I have to.
你终于准备好了吧
You're finally ready, right?
你没有其他选择
You know there's no other choice.
从来就没有
There's never been a choice.
我答应米迦勒
The answer is yes.
迪恩
Dean.
[咒语]
当然 我还有些条件
Of course, I have a few conditions.
- 你为什么改变主意 - 还不是这一堆破事儿
- What changed your mind? - The damnedest thing.
世界末日来临
I mean, the world's ending,
我们被压得不堪重负
The walls are coming down on us.
但是我不想让你失望
I just didn't want to let you down.
所以 去他妈的命运使然
So screw destiny.
我们用我们的方式 和他们斗争
I say we take the fight to them, do it our way.
（如今）
（孟西镇 印地安那州）
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
你好
Hi ya.
伙计 你不能来这儿
Buddy, you can't be here.
我当然可以
'course I can.
总得有人来做准备工作
Someone's got to get everything ready.
他们马上就到了 所有人
They're coming … all of them.
都会各司其职
And we've each got our part to play.
你也一样
Even you.
什么
What?
你是正餐
You're dinner.
这地方新开的啊
Nice digs, for once.
真忙啊
Busy night.
就像暴雨中的港口一样
Any port in a storm, I guess.
您先填下表
If you could just fill this out, please.
好的
Yeah.
先生 您这里有点
Sir, I think you got a little…
刮胡子留下的划痕
Shaving nick there.
你们的钥匙
Your key.
谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
你们这里不会连咖啡店都有吧
Hey, you wouldn't happen to have a coffee shop, would you?
有自助餐 请随便享用
Buffet. All you can eat.
我们有世上最好吃的派
Best pie in the tri-state area.
不是吧
You don't say?
天堂啊
Heaven, right?
相信我 伙计 天堂都没这儿好
Trust me, pal … better.
你好
How you doing?
别
No.
但是
But …
不
No.
小姐 我只是
Oh, lady, I'm just, you know …
我能理解
I understand.
还是不
And no.
不起作用
Didn't work.
萨姆 别皱眉 伙计 吃点东西
Sam, unpucker, man. Eat something.
我们应该继续赶路了
We should hit the road, dean.
冒这么大雨 真有点
In this storm? What? I-it's …
确切地说 是关于圣经中的事
It's biblical. Exactly.
现在本应是生死时速 可我们还在这儿吃派
I-it's friggin' noah's ark out there, and we're eating pie.
这周你才睡了几个小时
How many hours of sleep did you get this week?
三个还是四个
What? Three? Four?
鲍比已经在查了
Bobby's got his feelers out, okay?
我们也跟十二个州里
We have talked with every hoodoo man.
受害的男男女女都谈过了
And root woman in 12 states.
嗯 我没有放弃
Yeah, well, I'm not giving up.
没人说要放弃
Nobody's giving up.
尤其是我
Especially me.
我们会找到战胜路西法的办法的
We're gonna find a way to beat the devil, okay?
用不了多久 我能感觉得到
Soon. I can feel it.
我们也会找到卡西和亚当
And we will find Cass, we'll find Adam.
但身体是革命的本钱
But you are no good to me burnt out.
好吧
Yeah.
行 好的
Yeah, okay.
来吧 让我们过个清闲的晚上
Come on. We've actually got the night off for once.
享受一下吧
Let's try to enjoy it.
你多大了 才12吗
Oh, what are you, 12?
我有一颗年轻的心
I'm young at heart.
瞧瞧这儿
Wow. Look at this.
就像洛克菲勒家族一样
We're like Rockefellers.
巧克力
Chocolates!
你要吃你那份吗
You want yours?
你吃吧
Knock yourself out.
色情之家13号随时恭候
"Casa erotica 13" On demand.
怎么
What?
这个地方好像
Isn't this place kind of…
凭空出现
In the middle of nowhere?
那又怎样
So?
四星级酒店怎么会出现在荒芜的高速路旁
So what's four-star hotel doing on a no-star highway?
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
我们隔壁房间
The, uh, the room next to ours …
有一对男女刚才在亲热
T-the couple that are, uh, joined at the lips …
你看见他们了吗
Have you seen them?
洛根夫妇是吗 度蜜月的
Mr. And Mrs. Logan … the honeymooners?
他们已经结账走了
They checked out.
怎么了
Is something the matter?
他们退房了
They checked out?
是 就在刚才
Mm-hmm. Mm, just now.
真的吗
Really?
他们看起来似乎
It sort of seemed like they were, um…
正在做那事儿
…in the middle of something.
很奇怪 度蜜月的人退房时
Yeah, it's kind of weird for honeymooners.
竟把这个落下了
to, uh, check out without this.
天啊
Oh, dear.
我会把它放到失物招领处的
I'll just put that right in the lost and found.
别担心了
Don't you worry.
还需要什么帮助吗
Is there anything else I can help you with?
没 没问题了
Uh, no, no, we 're good.
好极了
Super-fantastic.
真诡异
Creepy.
别听他扯谈
Broke the needle.
这样吧 我对这块地方仔细检查
All right, well, I'll scope out the joint,
你盯着这个诺曼·贝茨（《精神病患者》中的旅馆连环杀手）
and you keep an eye on Norman Bates over here.
我说 这才一晚上
I mean, one night off.
问题也太多了
Is that too much to ask?
没见过人尿尿吗 伙计
There is no pees how, man!
你真美
You're beautiful.
嘴很甜啊
You're sweet.
我讨厌甜蜜
I hate sweet.
抱歉 打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
客人都到齐了
The last guest just arrived.
一切就绪了吗
So everything's ready?
向来如此
As it will ever be.
食品贮藏室已经满了
Pantry's full.
温彻斯特兄弟呢
And the Winchesters?
起了疑心 但在掌控之中
Suspicious, but under control.
你取到他们的血没
You have their blood?
当然
Of course I do.
我动作很快
I'm quick.
兄弟俩绝不会知道这伤哪儿来的
Boys never even knew what hit them.
谢谢 墨丘利
Thank you, Mercury.
很好 让我们开始典礼吧
Okay. Let's get this show on the road.
- 一头大象 - 是的
- An elephant? - Yeah.
一头真的大象吗
Like, an elephant?
像载人巴士那么大
Like, full-on the bus.
那这到底
So what the hell…
人都哪去了
Where is everybody?
让我来猜猜 门锁上了
Let me guess … it's locked.
怎么 蟑螂们只入住 不会退房吗
So, what? The roaches check in, they don't check out?
想想我们是怎么到这儿的
Think about how we got here.
90号公路上的临时绕行路
That detour on Line-90?
还有那该死的飓风
The friggin' hurricane?
你是说我们是被引导到这的
You saying we were led here?
像迷宫里的老鼠一样
Like rats in a maze.
拜托 一定要是番茄汤
Please be tomato soup.
一定要是番茄汤
《地狱旅馆》（1980年恐怖电影）
Motel hell.
救命 放我们出去
Help us! Get us out!
快点
Hurry up!
我已经尽快了
I'm going as fast as I can.
有人在我后面 对吧
There's somebody behind me, isn't there?
这可不像是个施里纳富人大集会
Something tells me this isn't a shriner convention.
晚餐准备好了
Dinner is served.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen…
我们尊贵的客人已经到了
Our guests of honor have arrived.
女士们 先生们 谢谢你们大驾光临
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for coming.
在我有生之年 从未想过能看到此情此景
Well, in all my centuries, I never thought I'd see this …
这么多神砥齐聚一堂
This many gods under one roof.
神灵
Gods?
在我们正式开始之前
Now, before we get down to brass tacks,
有些基本规则需要了解
some ground rules …
严禁互相屠杀
No slaughtering each other.
抑制你的怒火
Curb your wrath.
不要染指本地的处女们
Oh, and, uh, keep your hands off the local virgins.
我们在这得低调些
We're trying to keep a low profile here.
我们完蛋了
Oh, we are so, so screwed.
我们都知道聚集在此的原因
Now, we all know why we're here.
犹太基督教的天启笼罩了我们
The judeo-christian apocalypse looms over us.
我清楚我们在过去
I know we've all had our little disagreements.
有些小争议
in the past,
但现在该是不计前嫌
But the time has come to put those aside.
共创未来的时刻了
and look toward the future.
因为如果不这样 我们将没有明天
'cause if we don't, we won't have one.
我们现在有了两个极具价值的筹码
Now, we do have two very valuable bargaining chips …
米迦勒和路西法的皮囊
Michael and lucifer's vessels.
问题是
The question is…
我们现在该做什么
What do we do now?
谁有好点子 请发言
Anybody have any bright ideas, speak up.
这间屋子很安全
This is a safe room.
[汉语] 我们该做的
[汉语] 就是直接杀了他们
我可不喜欢这口气啊
Oh, I dot like his tone.
杀了他们 为什么
Kill them? Why?
为了让天使们再把他俩救活吗
So the angels here can bring them back again?
我搞不懂各位都在激动些啥
I don't know what everybody's getting so worked up about.
这只不过是两个天使打场架而已
This is just a couple of angels having a slap fight.
这不是世界末日大决战
It's no armageddon.
谁都知道战斗一结束
Everybody knows when the war comes to an end,
伟大的巨蟒约尔姆加德就会崛起
the great serpent jormungand rises up,
而我 就将成为巨狼的食物
and I, myself, will be eaten by a big wolf.
[汉语] 又来了
怎么 为什么这么说
Oh, ye? And why is that?
因为你的信仰更现实吗
Because your beliefs are so much more realistic?
整个世界不过是在巨龟背上
The whole world's getting carried around.
随身携带的玩意
on the back of a giant turtle.
少废话了吧
Give me a break.
[汉语] 别得罪我们的龟神
你能拿我怎么样
What are you gonna do about it?
[汉语] 让你卷铺盖滚到瓦尔哈拉殿
跟我说话时嘴巴放干净点 臭小子
You watch your mouth when you talk to me, boy!
[汉语] 臭小子 我比你大
没人证明过这点
No one's ever proved that.
别动
Stay.
我们必须战斗
We have to fight.
那些大天使
The archangels …
他们只热衷于暴力
the only thing they understand is violence.
只能是生死存亡的结局 没有别的出路
This ends in blood. There is no other way.
不是他们死 就是我们亡
It's them…or us.
恕我直言 女神
With all due respect… ma'am…
我们甚至都没有试着跟他们沟通过
we haven't even tried talking to them.
迦梨
Kali.
谁征求你的意见了
Who asked you?
难道我们就不能和平相处吗
Can't we all just get along?
加百
Gab…
萨姆 迪恩
Sam. Dean.
你们这俩笨蛋 总是在错误的时间
It's always wrong place, worst time.
出现在不该出现的地方
with you muttonheads, huh?
洛基
Loki.
巴尔德尔
Baldur.
我也很高兴见到你
Good seeing you, too.
看来我的请柬是寄丢了
I guess my invitation got lost in the mail.
你在这干什么
Why are you here?
和你谈谈那房子里的大象
To talk about the elephant in the room.
不是说你
Not you.
天启
The apocalypse.
伙计们 咱们是没法阻止的
We can stop it, gang.
但先说要事
But first things first.
我们成年人有事要谈
The adults need to have a little conversation.
回头找你们吧
Check you later.
镇定
Okay.
刚才
Did that…
真见鬼
Holy crap.
恩 绝对的
Yeah, tell me about it.
顺便说下 下次我提议接着赶路
By the way, next time I say "Let's keep driving, "
咱们就一直开车
uh, let's keep driving.
对 下次一定
Okay, yeah, next time.
好的 那咱们接下来咋办
Uh, all right, so, what's our next move?
我
I-I …
我也不知道
I don't know.
看来咱们得为冰箱里那些可怜人负责了
We grab those poor saps out of the freezer, I guess …
把他们救出来
Bust them out.
幸运的话 还能顺便干掉几个坏蛋
Gank a few freaks along the way if we're lucky.
你们哪辈子走运过
And when are you ever lucky?
哦 你管呢 咬我啊加百列
Oh, you know what? Bite me, Gabriel.
等会吧 小年青
Maybe later, big boy.
我就知道
I should have known.
这事一开始就像是你的风格
I mean, this had your stink all over it from the jump.
你觉得我是幕后黑手
You think I'm behind this?
拜托
Please.
我可是你们忠实的帮手
I'm the costner to your Houston.
是来救你的
I'm here to save your ass.
你想把我们拉出火坑
You want to pull us out of the fire?
答对了
Bingo.
那些神不是想把你们化成灰
Those gods are either gonna dust you.
就是想用你们做诱饵
or use you as bait.
不管咋样 你们都在劫难逃
Either way, you're uber-boned.
哦 可是几个月前
Wow … 'cause a couple of months ago,
你说我们得扮演好自己的角色
you were telling us that we need to play our roles.
你把我们往火坑里推呢
You were uber-boning us.
嘿 一切还没结束呢
Ohhhhh, the end is still nigh.
米迦勒和路西法还有戏要演
Michael and Lucifer are gonna dance the lambada.
不过不是今夜 不在这里
But not tonight. Not here.
这关你啥事
And why do you care?
我才不在乎呢
I don't care.
但是
But…
迦梨和我 我们
Me and Kali, we, uh…
有点私情
had a thing.
女人就是一切啊
Chick was all hands.
我能咋说 我挺多愁善感的
What can I say? I'm sentimental.
他们会赢吗
Do they have a chance?
会战胜撒旦吗
Against Satan?
萨姆你真这么想吗
Really, Sam?
迪恩你有别的办法吗
You got a better idea, Dean?
这可是个馊主意
It's a bad idea.
他们对路西法来说就是小儿科
Lucifer's gonna turn them into finger paint.
所以 趁着能开溜 咱们还是走吧
So let's get going while the going's good.
很好 那你干嘛不把我们传送出去呢
Okay, great. Why don't you just zap us out of here, then?
要能的话 我就这么干了
Would if I could.
但是迦梨有抓住了你们的小辫子
But Kali's got you by the short and curlies.
她用了个血咒
It's a blood spell.
你们俩被捆住了
You boys are on a leash.
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是 现在得用点古老的黑魔法了
Means it's time for a little of the old black magic.
好吧 随便你了
Okay. Yeah. Well, whatever.
我们要救出冰箱里的废物们
We're gonna take the all dirts in the freezer with us.
想都别想
Forget it.
把你们偷偷弄出去都够难的了
It's gonna be hard enough sneaking you mooks out of here.
他们叫你洛基 对吧
They called you "Loki, " Right?
就是说 他们还没弄明白你到底是谁
Which mean they don't really know who you are.
告诉过你 我在证人保护计划里面
Told you … I'm in witness protection.
这样吧 你按我们说的办
Okay, well, then how about you do what we say,
要不我们就跟那个异教神之组
or we tell the, uh, legion of doom.
讲讲你的秘密身份
about your secret identity?
他们看起来可不太像亲善的天使
They don't seem like a real pro-angel kind of crowd.
我让你变成哑巴
I'll take your voices away.
- 那我们就写下来 - 我砍掉你的手
- We'll write it down. - I'll cut off your hands.
那人们就会问了
Then people are gonna be asking,
你们怎么到处奔波却没有手
"why are you guys running around with no hands?"
好吧
Fine.
你好啊 我的爱
Bonjour, mon amour.
赶紧走
Leave.
你总喜欢装作难以获取芳心
You always did play hard to get.
我早都继续我的生活了
I've moved on.
我发现了
I noticed.
巴尔德尔
Baldur?
真的吗
Really?
巴尔德尔很单纯
Baldur's uncomplicated.
不
No!
不 不要
No, no!
不要 快停手
No! No! Stop!
不要啊
No!
太迟了
It's too late.
我没想到你会是这种型的
I never took you for the type.
浪漫型的吗
Romantic?
可怜兮兮的
Pathetic.
是你叫我来的
You're the one who call me here.
那是因为我以为你会认真对待这件事
Because I thought you might take this seriously.
我认真对待了啊
I'm taking this seriously.
世界末日要来了 大家该找出路了
Ship's sinking. Time to get off.
我是说 去他的地球 让我们去潘朵拉星球吧
I mean, screw this marble. Let's go check out Pandora.
不需要这样的
It doesn't have to be like that.
恐怕是这样的
Afraid it does.
要是我们抵抗
If we fight…
你就死了
You die.
你怎么这么肯定
And what makes you such an expert?
我和那些长着翅膀的红屁股猴子交过一两次手
I've tussled with those winged ass-monkeys once or twice.
伽梨 别再耍小手段
Kali… no more tricks.
我求你了 别这样做
I'm begging you … don't do this.
我必须要这么做
I have to.
不能怪我要劝你
Can't blame me for trying.
还爱我吗
Still love me?
不
No.
加百列死到哪里去了
Where the hell is Gabriel?
你肯定以为我是个傻子吧
You must take me for a fool…
加百列
Gabriel.
你现在属于我了
You're bound to me …
永远都是
now and forever.
猎鬼小分队
Ghostfacers!Ghostfacers!
Ghostfacers.
我们能找到见别人看不见的鬼魂
We face the ghosts when the others will not.
我们是猎鬼 猎鬼小分队
We're the ghost, ghostfacers.
一见鬼就退
They leave the kitchen when the kitchen gets hot.
还招实习生吗
Is the intern position open?
- 你被雇佣了 - 真的吗
- You're hired! - Really?
- 我的脸在那个显示屏吗 - 是的
- See my face right in your little box? - Yeah.
好的 我的脸要在画面中央
Okay, my face has got to be right in your box.
猎鬼小分队
Ghostfacers.
我们猎鬼 我们猎鬼
We face the faces, we face the ghosts.
猎鬼小分队
Ghostfacers.
要是你已经死了 好好死着
If you're dead, you better stay dead.
是
Yep.
要不然 我们会杀死你
'Cause if not, we're gonna kill you.
你什么时候知道的
How long have you known?
很早就知道了
Long enough.
营救计划进行的怎样啦
How's the rescue going?
好大的惊喜
Well, surprise, surprise.
我们被恶作剧精灵耍了
The trickster has tricked us.
伽梨 别这样
Kali…don't.
你现在是我的了
You're mine now.
你有我想要的东西
And you have something I want.
一把大天使的利刃
An archangel's blade.
属于大天使
From the archangel…
加百列的
Gabriel.
好吧 好吧
Okay!Okay!
我是有翅膀的
So I got wings.
跟护舒宝的护翼似的
Like Kotex.
但这也丝毫不影响我对路西法的判断
But that doesn't make me any less right about Lucifer.
他骗人
He's lying.
他是个间谍
He's a spy.
我不是间谍
I'm not a spy.
我是一个逃避者
I'm a runaway.
我试着救你
I'm trying to save you.
我了解自己的哥哥 伽梨
I know my brother, Kali.
他会把你们吓的魂飞魄散
He should scare the living crap out of you.
你们不可能打败他的
You can't beat him.
过程就不说了 我见过这个故事的最后结果
I've skipped ahead … seen how this story ends.
是你们的故事
Your story …
不是我们的
not ours.
西方人 都傲慢十足
Westerners … I swear, the sheer arrogance.
以为自己是地球上唯一的神族
You think you're the only ones on earth?
依仗着上帝的名义烧杀抢掠
You pillage and you butcher in your god's name.
但其实你们不是唯一的宗教神话
But you're not the only religion.
他也不是唯一的神祗
And he's not the only god.
你以为你们可以让地球分崩离析吗
And now you think you can just rip the planet apart?
你们错了
You're wrong.
世上有成千上万的神
There are billions of us.
我们是最先来这儿的
And we were here first.
要是有人活到世界的尽头
If anyone gets to end this world…
就是我
…it's me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
他们也会死
They can die.
我们可以杀死路西法
We can kill Lucifer.
是啊 你们这些原始野蛮的滑头
All right, you primitive screwheads.
听着
Listen up.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我别无选择
I'm out of options.
现在 等哪一天
Now, on any other given day,
我一定会杀了你们的
I'd be doing my damnedest to, uh, kill you,
你们这些肮脏血腥的黑猩猩
You filthy, murdering chimps.
但是
But, uh, hey…
现在是危急时刻
Desperate times.
所以即使我非常地想
So even though I'd love nothing better.
割开你们的喉咙 你们这帮混蛋
Than to slit your throats, you…dicks…
但我还是要帮你们
…I'm gonna help you.
我会帮你们解决掉路西法
I'm gonna help you ice the devil.
然后照例 我们就可以互杀了
And then we can all get back to ganking each other, like normal.
你们想要路西法
You want Lucifer?
他的名字可不在电话薄上
Well, dude's not in the yellow pages.
但是我很萨姆 我们可以把他引到这里
But me and Sam, we can get him here.
怎么做
How?
首先 你要先把那些主菜端走
First, you let those main courses go.
然后我们再说
Then we talk.
我们要么就一起对付路西法
We can either take on the devil together.
要不你们这些混蛋可以吃掉我
Or you lame-ass bitches can eat me.
没有比喻的意思
Literally.
快点 大家快走
Come on, everybody! Let's go!
走 走 走 走
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
好的 好的
All right. All right.
走 走 走 离开这里
Go! Go! Go! Get out of here!
喂 迪恩
Psst! Dean!
别望向我
D… t Don'look at me.
表现自然点儿
Act natural.
上车
Get in.
老兄 我今天就没碰上自然的事
Man, there is nothing natural about this at all.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
你以为我会让迦梨拿到我的真刃
You think I'd give Kali my real sword?
那东西可以杀死我呀
That thing can kill me.
那他们拿的是什么
Then what do they have in there?
假的
A fake.
我用一听橙子片变的
Made it out of a can of diet orange slice.
那么
So, uh…
去把我们的血偷回来吧
Go snag our blood, would ya?
什么
What?
我听到你们讲话了
I heard you in there.
迦梨喜欢你 你能混进去
Kali likes you. You can get close.
血浆一到手 我们就可以溜了
Lift the plasma, then we vamoose.
不行
No.
把真刃交出来
Hand over the real blade.
或者干脆硬气点站出来
Better yet, why don't you sack up.
帮我们消灭路西法
And help us take down Lucifer?
- 你开玩笑的吧 - 我认真的
- You can't be serious. - Deadly.
你何时开始跟怪物穿一条腿裤子了
Since when are you butt-buddies with a bunch of monsters?
他们在你眼里就是怪物 我有说错吗
That's all they are to you, aren't they?
我知道 萨姆说得对 我是疯了
All right, you know what? Sam was right. It's nuts.
但这是我最好的主意
But it's the best idea I've heard.
除非你还有高招
So unless you have a better one…
好吧 祝你好运
Well, good luck with that.
我呢 出去凉快着
Me, I'm blowing John's town.
那群旅鼠要跳崖
Those lemmings want to run off a clif.
不关我的事
That's their business.
我看透你了 知道吗
I see right through you. You know that?
总说聪明话 一副满不在乎的表情
The smart-ass shell, the whole "I could give a crap" thing.
相信我 我再清楚不过了
Believe me, it takes one to know one.
- 是嘛 - 正是
- That so? - Yes.
里面那些怪物跟你或许不是血亲
And maybe those freaks in there aren't your blood,
但也算是同族
But they are your family.
他们刚刚把我一剑穿心了呢
They just stabbed me in the friggin' heart!
就算如此你还是关心他们 不是吗
Maybe, but you still give a crap about them, don't you?
迪恩
Dean …
你再不出手 他们就死定了
Now, they're gonna die in there without you.
我不能杀自己的哥哥
I can't kill my brother.
是不能 还是不愿
"Can't" Or "Won't"?
我就知道
That's what I thought.
由你来召唤路西法
So, you're going to summon Lucifer?
算是吧
Sort of.
只要你们帮我把肋骨上的印记消掉
I just need you to squeegee some stuff from my ribs,
他顷刻就到
And he'll come running.
直接弄折不是更简单
Breaking them would be easier.
演出到此结束
Show's over.
刃是假的
Sword's a fake.
加百列依旧活蹦乱跳
And Gabriel … he's still kicking.
真不想告诉你 大姐 你被人耍了
I hate to break it to you, sister, but you've been tricked.
入住
Checking in.
路西法
Lucifer.
感谢光临
Thanks for coming.
呼唤我 算你识相
Oh, you did right calling me.
就是
It's just…
里面那些家伙的想法 有点
The way the talk is heading in there, it's…
太疯狂了
It's insane.
知道吗 我真不理解你们这些异教徒
You know, I never understood you pagans.
你们这群 渺小的东西
You're such… petty little things.
总是杀来杀去
Always fighting…
相互出卖 乐此不疲
Always happy to sell out your own kind.
难怪地球最终归了我们
No wonder you forfeited this planet to us.
你们比人类更糟糕
You are worse than humans.
甚至比恶魔更糟糕
You're worse than demons.
却又自称为神
And yet you claim to be gods.
他们还说我傲慢呢
And they call me prideful.
出什么事了
What's happening?
是他
It's him.
怎么可能
How?
没意义了
Does it matter?
把我们都瞬移出去
Shazam us out of here, would you?
做不到了
We can't.
当然做不到
Of course you can't.
没请示妈咪不能出门
You didn't say "Mother, may I?"
萨姆 迪恩 很高兴又见面了
Sam, Dean. Good to see you again.
巴尔德尔 别
Baldur…don't.
你以为这地球是你的
You think you own the planet?
谁给你的权力
What gives you the right?!
权力不是给的
No one gives us the right.
是夺来的
We take it.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
有事
Not really.
迟到总比不到强
Better late than never, huh?
用生命看好它
Guard this with your life.
小路
Lucy.
我回来了
I'm home.
这次不行
Not this time.
伙计们
Guys!
带她离开
Get her out of here.
为了一个女人
Over a girl.
加百列 你不是吧
Gabriel, really?
我知道你一向不大检点 但是这也
I mean, I knew you were slumming, but…
希望你没传上病
I hope you didn't catch anything.
路西法
Lucifer…
你是我兄弟 我爱你
You're my brother, and I love you.
可你真是个超级大混球
But you are a great big bag of dicks.
你刚说我什么
What did you just say to me?
看看你自己
Look at yourself.
诶呀呀
"Boo-hoo.
老爸凶我了 所以我要把他的玩具都砸烂
Daddy was mean to me, so I'm gonna smash up all his toys."
讲话注意点
Watch your tone.
随你怎么装受伤者
Play the victim all you want.
可你我之间 大家心里知道
But you and me … we know the truth.
老爸最爱的是你
Dad loved you best.
超过米迦勒
More than Micheal.
超过我
More than me.
可自从他带了新宝宝回家
Then he brought the new baby home,
你就受不了了
And you couldn't handle it.
所以这一切仅仅是你的出气筒
So all this is just a great big temper tantrum.
该成熟点了
Time to grow up.
我才不会坐这个东西
I'm not getting in that thing.
请上车 公主
Just get in the car, princess.
加百利 如果你是为米迦勒做事
Gabriel, if you're doing this for michael …
去他的
screw him.
如果他站在这里 我一样做了他
If he were standing here, I'd shiv his ass, too.
你背叛了
You disloyal …
不 我对他们
Oh, I'm loyal,
很忠诚
to them.
谁
Who?
这些 所谓的天神吗
These…so-called gods?
是对人类忠诚 路西法.
To people, Lucifer.
人类
People.
你就为了这群蟑螂 心甘情愿去死吗
So you're willing to die for a pile of cockroaches?
为什么
Why?
因为父亲是对的
Because dad was right.
他们比我们优秀
They are better than us.
人类是残缺不全 缺陷百出的弃物
They are broken, flawed abortions.
他们确实有缺陷
Damn right they're flawed.
但是大多数人都 努力让自己更好
But a lot of them try… to do better.
学会原谅
To forgive.
或许你应该去脱衣舞俱乐部逛逛
And you should see the Spearmint Rhino.
我已经坐了太久的冷板凳了
I've been riding the pine a long time,
现在我要重回战斗了
but I'm in the game now.
你和米迦勒 我谁都不帮
And I'm not on your side or Michael's.
我为人类而战
I'm on theirs.
兄弟 不要逼我这么做
Brother, don't make me do this.
没人逼我们做任何事
No one makes us do anything.
加百利 你认为自己的奸计得逞了吗
I know you think you're doing the right thing, Gabriel.
我知道你的真身在哪里
But I know where your heart truly lies.
在这里
Here.
你的戏法太业余了
Amateur hocus-pocus.
别忘了
Don't forget …
你的戏法都是我传授的 弟弟
you learned all your tricks from me, little brother.
（该影片中的所有内容）
（十八岁以下不得观看）
（卡萨色情 第十三号）
亲爱的日记
Dear diary…
做一个拥有无上权力的集团总裁太有趣了
being a high-powered business president is super-fun,
但也很辛苦
but so exhausting.
有时候我真的需要好好休息一下
Sometimes I just need to relax.
我需要 色情之家
I need…Casa Erotica.
客房服务
Room service.
请进
Come in!
这就是加百利让你用生命保护的东西吗
Gabriel wanted you to guard this with your life?
可能他是剧迷吧
Maybe he's a fan.
这部剧不错
It is a good one.
我送来了你订的波兰熏肠
I've got the kielbasa you ordered.
波兰的吗
Polish?
匈牙利的
Hungarian.
他到底在干什么
What the hell's going on?
萨姆 迪恩
Sam. Dean.
你们可能很困惑我到底在干什么
You're probably wondering what the hell's going on.
好吧
Well…
如果你们在看这个
If you're watching this…
那我就已经死了
I'm dead.
拜托
Oh, please!
别悲泣
Stop sobbing.
这让我们都很尴尬
It's embarrassing for all of us.
没有我
Without me,
你们杀死路西法的几率就等于零
you've got zero shot at killing Lucifer.
很抱歉
Sorry.
但是
But…
你们可以困住他
you can trap him.
那个关路西法的牢笼 仍然在下面
The cage you sprung lucifer from is still down there.
那么你们 也许 可以把他关回去
And maybe … just maybe … you can shove his ass back in.
当然不是那么容易
Not that it'll be easy.
你们先要打开牢笼 然后把他骗进去
You got to get the cage open, trick my bro back into it,
还有
And, uh … oh, yeah …
避开米迦勒和上帝使团
avoid Michael and the God squad.
但是 还不够具体 对吧
But hey, details, right?
我有个惊天大秘密
And here's the big secret,
连路西法自己也不知道
Lucifer himself doesn't even know.
牢笼的钥匙 就在世间
But the key to the cage … it's out there.
事实上 不止一把钥匙
Actually, it's keys … plural.
有四把钥匙
Four keys.
更详细一点 四个戒指
Well, four rings.
天启四骑士的戒指
From the horsemen.
找全了戒指 就可以打开牢笼
You get them all, you got the cage.
不能说我完全我在把赌注压在你们身上
Can't say I'm betting on you boys,
不过呢 我曾经犯过错误
but, uh, hey, I've been wrong before.
迪恩
And, Dean…
你是正确的
you were right.
我害怕对抗我的哥哥
I was afraid to stand up to my brother.
但是我不再害怕了
Not anymore.
现在我站起来了
So this is me standing up.
现在我又要
And this is me…
躺下了
Lying down.
老兄
Oh! Oh, man.
天启四骑士 啊
Horsemen, huh?
我们拿到了战争骑士的
Well, we got war's.
我们还拿到了饥饿骑士的
We nicked famine's.
我们有两个戒指了
That's two rings down.
只需要拿到瘟疫和死亡的
Collect all four,
我们就凑齐四枚戒指了
just need pestilence and death.
就这样吗
Oh, is that all?
还是个计划
It's a plan.
搞什么
What the hell?
这个东西会不会让人打瞌睡
Does this stuff make you drowsy?
我还要开很久的车
I got a lot of driving to do.
蓝色的会让你犯困
Blue ones make you sleepy.
红色的和橘色的可以在白天吃
Red and orange ones are okay for daytime.
这 这太可怕了
This is … this is awful.
（内华达）